This love in my heart,
it will burn on forever!
Granting me courage, I
hope it will never stop!
No matter where you
are, nothing is too far!
With our everlasting bones,
we'll reach it, we are home!
I'm
so truly grateful!
I ran into you on that day so long ago!
We laughed every moment
with tears in our eyes!
Till we knew we weren't alone!
The blowing wind came in
and joined us on our way!
And with it I know we'll rise!
We'll be flying up high!
Why, tell me why are you giving up?
Why, tell me why you want to fight alone?
Hey, what kind of future
do you think you have?
Your dream is already in your hands.
This love in my heart,
it will burn off forever.
Granting me courage, I
hope it will never stop.
I don't matter where you
are, nothing is too far.
With our everlasting
plans, we'll reach it.
We are home from the horizon,
out on the edge of the world.
If there is a place that
I'd want to take you to?
Let's head for it then!
But as for the way, we already know.
We promised it long ago.
You scream by your voice.
That can't break through the silence?
Feeling defeated.
It crushes your helpless heart.
I've got your back, I swear.
I'll always be here.
Let's put our fate within
this light under the sun.
Can you close your eyes and
just listen to my voice?
Let's find the answer together.
I'm telling you in our path.
I trust that it will lead us.
To another sea untarded.
Cause now we are home.
On the horizon, out on
the edge of the world.
There is a place I want to take you to.
Let's head for it then.
But as for the way we already know.
We promised it long ago.
Are you really gonna wait here?
We're right in the middle
of enemy territory.
Oh, wait!
Remember what Pound said?
About the last person who
took out a sweet general?
Big Mom summoned a storm along
with an army hungry for revenge.
and their target didn't survive an instant
so we know that the enemy will come,
but Sanji on the other
hand, Sanji will be back!
I'll wait just like I said.
Chess look at mine, handsome foliage,
it's been ruined, chopped down.
What's going on?
It was clear only a second ago.
Where are those clouds coming from?
kingbaum, what's causing all this?
It's coming from the whole
cake Shit where mama lives.
Her fury is tremendous.
Then those clouds—are
hers?
No
way!
All
that power—coming from
one person!
My climate
tax can't hold a candle
to something like that.
Linlin can
command the weather quite literally.
quite literally
Once her rage is awakened, there's
nothing in this world that can stop her!
Zeus and Prometheus are
running wild up there!
Mama's mad.
I'm really mad.
Clear the way!
The forces of fury are marching!
They're off to avenge General Cracker.
Make way!
Move it, you idiots!
Ha ha ha!
A whole army!
They're hunting down Straw Hat, no doubt.
The rat's as good as dead now.
Wow, that's funny.
He won't run because he's
waiting for his old pal Sanji.
Good thing you said your goodbyes.
Aw, damn!
That's Bobbin the Disposer!
Amand the Mademoiselle!
And Mondor the Scribe!
Wonder how much all
those bounties add up to.
I'm staying right here and
I'm not moving on a hitch!
Who am I kidding?
Even Straw Hat wouldn't
be stupid enough to
sit around after getting
a load of that army.
It's raining.
This is...
syrup, I think.
Uh, what's wrong?
I won't eat syrup or anything,
not unless Sanji's the one cooking it.
Mama's here!
Are you being good, boys and girls?
Mama, I've got a problem.
What is it, Inanna?
The head chef's being mean
and won't let me use a knife.
I just wanna cut open my dolly.
That won't do at all, will it?
Hey, Dials and Dragé,
go and get her a knife.
No way, no how, Mama.
She says she wants to cut her dolly,
but she's gonna pop our balloon.
Yeah, she's a bad girl, and I'm
gonna kill her someday for sure.
Mama, kill her first.
We shouldn't say mean things like
that to each other, should we, Mama?
Ha ha ha ha!
It's only natural.
Everyone has a couple hundred
people that they want dead.
But let's hold off on the
killing for now, all right?
Your big sister pudding is getting
married tomorrow, you know?
Aren't you excited?
We'll have a delicious wedding
cake, big enough for everyone.
Hooray! Hooray! Yay!
Now, this should be fun.
I'm going to meet the
Groob's family. D 'or!
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Ma, ma, ma, ma, ma.
It's truly a pleasure to have
you here, Jeremiah Double Six.
Sorry if I'm late.
So that's Big Mom.
I had a little hiccup to take care of.
Everything should be peachy now.
Oh, Pudding!
There you are!
Pardon the delay.
You know, I've heard so
much about Sanji already.
What a coincidence that he's a chef.
Why, he's a perfect match for my Pudding.
Well, they're getting married
either way, so it doesn't matter.
This is strictly a political arrangement.
But it's lovely that we can find something
that works to our mutual benefit, Judge.
Indeed.
Though it would make me even happier
if our children could share in the joy.
Let's give them a perfect wedding.
A toast to their future.
Black tea, green tea, choose please!
Uh, black? Yeah!
Take a bite, also nice!
Liza, please start with me!
Liza, won't you start with me?
I know just a thing you need,
have a bit of sweet, honey!
It's very sweet!
I usually don't hate food but I hate you.
Noisiest damn food I've ever seen.
You, don't it taste so yummy?
Um, Sanji.
We are kaput.
We are Gatling, I say.
No way.
There's too many.
Luffy.
Come on, please, you just need to get
out of here and hide for a little while.
You can come back later!
You're not breaking your word,
I won't go—what happens if Saji
comes back here while I'm gone?
It's okay, leave this fight to me, Lupi.
This is impossible—we're in the
middle of an emperor's territory.
emperor's territory
It's an entire army!
There's no way you can win!
Shawhead Nico is now in sight!
I told him I would be here!
I won't break my promise!
You led my friends to this island?
I'm sorry.
I gave Luffy my word that I
would bring you to the southwest
coast so you would be able
to get away from Mama safely.
But I couldn't make it happen, and
now they're all in grave danger.
I see now.
I wondered how they managed to pass
through all that security to get here.
It was thanks to you.
I know you meant well.
That said, no matter what, I still
wouldn't have gone to the coast.
If you're worried about the invitation,
you can let me take the blame.
She's my mom.
I'll be fine.
Just don't show up at the ceremony.
She's used to arranged marriages,
so she puts special bracelets on people
who seem like they might run away.
If you try to leave the island
with one, I know it explodes.
Your mom has the key to unlock this thing.
If I want to get it, then I have
to defeat the big mom pirates.
So she's already gotten to you sadly.
Yeah, she's thinking ahead, and
even if that weren't the case,
no one here has my back,
even
though
we're brothers.
They still did this.
Your own family beat you that badly?
That's right.
But why?
Because to them, I'm just a failure
who shouldn't be allowed to live.
I've never once been happy
about being born as royalty.
That's the reason I went out to sea.
Searching for a place I
wasn't even sure was real.
And now,
if I try to prevent
this arranged marriage,
they'll slaughter all my friends and me.
On top of that, they're going to kill the
man in the East Blue who saved my life.
The man who I respect as my real father.
No matter what I do at this
point, there's no way out.
Which is why I've decided that
I won't fight this anymore.
I'm willing to accept this
marriage on one condition.
I want Big Mom to let
my friends go unharmed.
Our soldiers are out there
attacking as we speak.
I'm so sorry.
You're in such pain,
and it's all because of what I did,
pudding—it's not your fault. I promise.
years ago,
I managed to escape hell only
to walk right back in again.
But
I should try to be happy after all—I
was free for all of these years, right?
The friends
who helped me improve as a chef, and the
companions who joined me in my travels.
I'm grateful
to all of the people I met out there.
And I
can't bear to hurt them.
That's why
my adventure ends here.
Hey, don't
cry!
It makes me feel worse.
feel worse
Look, it's okay.
But listen.
Sanji.
I promise.
If you decide to marry me,
I won't let it be hell.
Oh dear, what am I saying?
You're suffering so much and
I'm making everything about me.
You don't want to marry me, so of
course this would be hell for you.
Why am I being so insensitive
at a time like this?
It's awful, I'm so embarrassed after
all you and I have only just met,
so how could I possibly hope to fill the
hole in your heart, and besides all that.
You still might change your mind,
so I was being presumptuous, too.
You're my salvation.
What are you saying?
Pudding, if you'll have me.
I want us to get married tomorrow.
Hey, what gives?
Get down here!
Stop!
You don't look like anything special,
so I wasn't expecting power like that.
I suppose I should have paid
better attention to you.
Oh, my God.
Bane's Blade
Shirado But I'm innocent, ma 'am.
Please, you've got to believe me!
Amad, please!
Now slow, bow it.
It hurts!
Ah!
This is cruel!
Could you at least cut me down quickly?
If I were to finish you off in one
swing, there wouldn't be any point.
That's why I sliced through my enemies
as slowly and painfully as possible.
You are something else, Straw Hat.
You stayed up all night long fighting
with our big brother Cracker.
And it hasn't slowed you down one bit.
Those chest peacekeepers
are pretty sturdy.
But you're tearing right through them.
Now, come with us!
The cream monster!
What's that?
It's burning!
Sweet cream is always best
when it's fresh and piping hot!
And by the time the cream
reaches the perfect temperature,
your entire body will be
toasted like a marshmallow.
Now Gum-Gum!
Sorry, kid, but that one's
not gonna work for me.
Elephant Gum-Gum!
What the?
Hey, where am I?
And I welcome you to the World of Books!
Oh, but I keep getting burned!
Enough already!
A dream monster!
Oh, no!
Knock it off!
Loopy! Here they come!
Watch out!
King Baal.
the chess peacekeepers happen to be homies
so this explains why
they couldn't defeat you
it also tells us how
you were able to escape
from the seducing woods
everything makes sense
now how in the hell did you
get your hands on mama's vibre
card it has lola's name on
it what did you just say our
lola did you steal it from
her you mean she's dead the
girl never should have run
away like that lola and why did
you kill her hold on she gave
it to me i'm her friend i
doubt it yeah try telling mama
that unfortunately our orders
were to bring you back alive
let's go just look at that
mess almost all of the chest
peace keepers were wiped out
I told Sanji, I'd wait here.
I have to.
No matter what.
I'm sorry, would you like a bite?
No.
I came here to ask you for a favor.
Don't you worry about the Straw Hats.
The crew members you're currently
aligned with will be free to leave.
I promise I'll give you my word on it.
Just forget the idea of running away.
Marry my daughter without making a fuss.
And poof, it'll be like nothing ever has.
Thank you so much.
I swear I'll do everything
I can to make pudding happy.
Your head over heels in love
with my little girl, aren't you?
It warms my heart.
But let me make this clear.
The Straw Hats have done a
truly unspeakable thing to me.
Under normal circumstances,
I'd make sure they pay.
They have destroyed my seducing woods.
And defeated one of my
three sweet generals.
Also, back on Fishman Island,
your captain devoured my candies!
and had the gall to pick a fight with me.
But that's all in the past.
Right now, your wedding
is my top priority.
And if it's a success,
then by this time tomorrow,
all of Jerma's forces will be mine.
And then right after that,
we will all get to celebrate together by
tucking into a big, delicious wedding cake.
As long as you don't run away, Hey, the
whole situation will tidy up nicely.
All right, Sanji.
Yeah.
Supposement, there are 30 or so of these
bonoglyphs scattered out travers le Monda.
Their inscriptions, carved on
stone tablets Kuma Vice voyez ici,
have remained unbroken
for hundreds of years.
Only nine of those certain monoglyphs
have l 'information spécifique,
but they are très important to bear it.
For, if you take their
massage to the final island,
laugh-tell, then the truth of the world
will be revealed selon la légende!
Please, no!
General Smoothie, stop!
I'll do anything!
Have mercy, General Smoothie!
General Smoothie!
However, in order to actually
reach Laugh Tale en premier lieu,
You need something else.
The four road poneglyphs,
which are colored red.
Recently, Jinbe delivered
one to us, as you may know.
A gift for you.
I just picked it up by chance. Like me!
So, au total, the big mom pirate possess.
Two ordinary poneglyphs
and un road poneglyph.
Three stones precious carefully
sealed away right here.
Yeah, the stones are
important. I get that.
My question is, why did you tighten security
all of a sudden with no explanation?
Not that I mind guarding them.
After all, I'm free. Till the party.
Merci.
I apologize for calling you so suddenly.
But we're dealing with a former pirate
captain who came to this
island five years ago.
His objective during his last unwelcome
visit was to steal Poneglyphs,
so we may assume the sneaky meek
is attempting the same again.
Uh-oh.
He was only spared because his
compagnon becomes begged for his life,
so his decision to return is
both confounding and foolish.
Why, Pedro?
One might say,
the road upon the glyphs are la plus
grande importance to any pirate crew.
You can become king of
the pirates with them.
A quest worthy of the four emperors,
n 'est-ce pas, sweet general smoothie?
On conclusion,
we must take every
precaution possible and put
our very lives on the land
to protect these storms.
You're back.
Damn it!
They called in more guards? Indeed.
A woman with long legs.
Frightening, but lovely.
Her name's Smoothie.
A sweet general, they said.
Frankly, I feared as much.
She did look quite imposing.
All hope is lost.
Even at night, we wouldn't have a chance.
Not with their security like that.
Our last chance vanished the instant
that Baron Tamago noticed I was here.
Things haven't gone
quite smoothly for Luffy.
So it would have been nice if our
plan had been successful, at least.
You know, I was rather touched by
what you said before we came here.
If Luffy really is going to
become the king of the pirates,
then he'll need that road
poneglyph eventually.
We have to face that fact.
That said, if we retreat from here
now, it would be hard to come back.
Just think,
you and I have made it all the way to
our destination without a single fight.
If we tried again later, there's
no guarantee we'd have such luck.
True enough.
So even if things look dicey, this could
be a once in a lifetime chance for us.
Still, if we attack, we'll both be killed.
Who is Baron Tamago's target?
It's me.
Perhaps you could serve as the bait, then?
Actually, I was just
thinking the same thing.